itftennis.com 2010-06-23

# ITF Tennis - About the ITF - Privacy Policy

The following provides detail about our Privacy Policy.   
We treat your privacy seriously.

_Notice: This policy only applies to web sites run by ITF and not to the companies, individuals, organisations or other web sites to which there are links._

**Consent**

Your use of this web site signifies your consent to us collecting and using personal information about you as specified below in accordance with this Policy. Should we choose to change our Policy for any reason, the changes will be posted here, so that you are always kept informed of how we collect and use your personal information, and when we may disclose it. 

**How Do We Collect Information About You And How Is It Used?**

You may provide personal information when communicating with us.

You may order a product or a service and give your name, email address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date so that the order can be processed and your products (or services where appropriate) delivered to you. Sometimes you may be asked for your telephone number.

You may provide data in connection with tournaments and rankings which may be published on the net.

If you enter a competition or promotion we will ask for your name, address and Email address.

We will collect information about your tastes and preferences both when you tell us what these are and by analysis of customer traffic, including by using cookies (see below).

It may be that some of the personal information you give us (for instance about your lifestyle or health) is sensitive personal data within the meaning of the Data Protection Act 1998. Any such information ("sensitive information") will only be disclosed with your express consent.

It may be that you provide to us details of credit or debit cards or bank accounts in order to make payments to us.

We may use personal information collected about you to personalise your visits to our web site and recommend goods or services to you. We also use the information to help us develop the design and layout of our web site to ensure that our sites are as useful and enjoyable as possible.

We may use personal information collected about you to let you know about functionality changes to our web site or changes to our terms and conditions of use.

Sometimes (and only in accordance with preferences selected by you) we or our affiliated companies might use the personal information collected about you to let you know about, new goods, services or offers that you might find interesting. If you do not wish to receive such information please email us using our [feedback form](http://www.itftennis.com/abouttheitf/feedback.asp?userid=8).

**Traffic Data**

We may provide aggregate statistics about our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other site information to third parties, but these statistics will not include any information that could personally identify you.

**Other Disclosures**

We reserve the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its users.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We have strict security procedures covering the storage and disclosure of your information in order to prevent unauthorised access and to comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. This means that sometimes we may ask you for proof of identity before disclosing any personal information to you.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. We may use cookies to identify returning visitors to our websites and obtain information about your last visit. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our web site, including purchasing items.

^ [Back to Top](http://www.itftennis.com/abouttheitf/legal/privacy.asp#top)
